It's an actual creature that I can't feel
like I'm being a particular creature.
I am a little under the sky.
I am free 쿠komi's face to face.
It'll be a little before we pass.
Just look at the other
spots you see in the clouds.
If you want to see a new world,
we will live in the vakit world.
I'll see you
next
time.
Hey, does this door look familiar to you?
Yes, it looks more than familiar.
It even has a nameplate.
This doesn't fit here at all!
Yeah!
What?
It really is my blood!
Even the garbage I forgot to take
out is here in perfect detail!
What is up with that goddess?
I really don't understand
what this skill is about.
Right now, all I can think about is
getting you back to your place safely.
I see.
It's because of what I said.
the manner in which she
grants wishes is a little bit
sloppy well the water and
electricity both work but the
TV not so much the windows
don't open and it's pitch
-black outside still a pretty
useful ability though you know
those bites are enormous I'm reminded of a
hamster more than anything else well Well,
at any rate, at least we won't have trouble
finding food or a decent place to sleep.
Hmm?
Food will be a problem though, won't it?
This is all I have in the house.
All gone.
The last food?
The last food.
You only have one serving?
Why the heck would you
casually eat it right now?
Well, I mean, I was hungry!
You have nothing set
aside for emergencies? No!
Because I never eat at home!
Don't you get it?
What were you planning to do if there
were a giant earthquake or something?
I knew if that happened, you'd
come and save me anyway, right?
Well, you're a fault for
being so overprotective!
Then hurry up and become
independent, idiot.
We do have water, so we should
be able to manage for a week.
Worst case scenario, we could break
down that bear thing from meat.
There's no way I'm ever gonna
eat something like that.
My god, you really are
spoiled, aren't you?
Well, none of this changes
what we have to do.
Gather information and secure food.
We should move while we still can.
You mean we have to keep
hiking up that mountain?
No, I think we'll be done
with that fairly soon.
Actually earlier, while we were
being chased, I saw some smoke.
I think there might be
a settlement that way.
Aww!
Whoa!
It's so fantasy-esque!
It definitely doesn't look like Japan.
But, uh, how can I put it?
Will I be okay dressed like this?
I wish I could approve, but...
I can't.
It's not like I'm wearing this
because I want to, you know?
I only had these because my sister
left them behind when she visited!
That's true.
There's nothing to be done.
I don't get it.
Do you realize you've been pretty
cold to me ever since this happened?
I've always been like this.
Maybe you're self-conscious
since you've got this new body.
Do you think?
Yeah, I guess.
But it's still hard to look at
you, so you need new clothes ASAP.
I know.
We need to hurry up and find
some clothes from this world.
Do it just as we planned. Got it.
I'm a rich young lady from a remote region
and you're here with me as my attendant.
And I can't say why I'm traveling,
but that explains why I
don't know this area at all.
And that's all she wrote.
Yeah, sure, that sounds about right.
Just watch and learn.
With this beauty and my great
communication skills, I'll be unstoppable.
I can make any man out
there fall in love with me.
Oh yeah!
You never succeed with women.
Shut your face!
Seriously?
It's true.
Those looks will prove advantageous.
Even without knowing the language,
it's unlikely things will go poorly.
Tachibana is a good communicator.
Isn't that too much smoke
for such a small settlement?
And it smells charred.
We've got bandits!
Run!
Leave everything behind!
It's me! Help me!
Help!
Tachibana!
What's the commotion?
Are they having a festival?
Out of the way!
Ma 'am, now my clothes are dirty.
You're not hurt, are you, young miss?
Oh, I'm sorry to bother
you while you're working.
It's just that I'm a little lost, you see.
Huh?
Oh, do you maybe not understand me?
Bonjour!
Excuse-moi!
Is...is this...could this be...true love?
Wait, uh...is this a dangerous situation?
I thought you were a woodcutter.
Will you marry me?
Say what?
I'd quit leaving if it were for you.
I'm fully prepared to live a decent life.
We can grow vegetables or
something, and I want two children.
What is this all of a sudden?
Now that that's settled,
I'll get permission from the boss
and head back to my home country.
Hey!
Hang on a sec!
Whoa, whoa, why are you
playing around over here?
Big bro, look!
I've just found myself
a cute wife! A wife?
What are you going on about?
Will you marry me?
Why?
I'd quit thieving if it were for you.
And I'm prepared to live a decent life.
We can make clay pots or something.
And I want eight children.
How many kids do these
guys want me to have?
So this is what that meant?
Is that what's going on?
My beauty really pushes people this far?
No one steals my wife away!
Not even you, big bro!
She will spend her life with me!
This calls for a duel! Marry me.
I'd quit thieving if it were for you.
No, you won't! Back off!
What do you think you're doing?!
This is my fault!
Please stop fighting!
This is all so pointless,
I'm not gonna marry anyone!
Are you safe, Tachibana?!
Not for my sake, not for me!
I beg you, don't fight!
Oh wow did you do this
I haven't done anything
all I did was exist but I I they started
fighting Because I'm just too beautiful
Tachibana you're actually
loving this aren't you
Thank you oh beautiful
one thank you and now
it seems I'm being revered
like I'm some kind of
Deity well it's a whole
lot healthier than that
fight that broke out
earlier I really have become
A woman of such beauty
that I couldn't possibly
exist I just thought I
might be a little bit
Popular I underestimate
it too I think I finally
kind of understand why
you started hating women
What no because if this
stuff happens everywhere I
go that'll be oh maybe I should
hide my face Well, does it work?
No, but some countermeasures
do seem like a good idea.
Now that I think about it, why
doesn't it affect you, though?
Hm?
Uh, you mean why am I fine
when these guys aren't?
Must be because I know
you're a man. I see.
I'm not exactly unaffected, though.
Maybe it's got something to do with the
intelligence setting and the parameters?
I bet it's got some kind of mental effect.
Crap! We're defeated!
To think we'd get wiped
out by a lone woman.
But you'd do well to be afraid,
because we're an advance party.
So, in just a few hours, the main
group will realize something's wrong,
and they'll get ready to fight,
and then they'll come here for you!
We haven't said a single word.
They're having a
conversation with themselves.
I'm really looking forward
to seeing this entire
village get crushed into
the ground like a grave!
If they're close enough to
guess something's wrong,
that means their stronghold is nearby.
Are these guys for real?
Where is it?
You think I'm stupid?
I'm not telling you! Tachibana?
Well, you give me no choice.
I really wish you'd tell me!
Could it be that I'm undefeatable?
What are you waiting for?
Let's go.
So cute!
Well, I guess they would have lookouts.
Seems our enemies aren't fools.
I do like that we can check
their strengths ahead of time.
You can see other people's stats, too?
Their numbers are low compared to yours.
The thing is, we don't know
how far we can trust these.
And we can't know how many are inside.
We'll tread carefully.
That's no fun at all.
Why don't you just smack
them around a little
bit and finish this up
before it gets started?
You took out that beam-shooting
bear with one punch, you can do it!
You make it sound so easy.
Back when you were student council
president, you took out a den of delinquents.
Same thing, right?
Different danger level entirely!
Also, I didn't take them out.
I just rehabilitated them.
You call that rehab?
Well, then should I go?
Seriously?
What can you do with those
cannon fodder level stats?
Don't go thinking that cannon
fodder isn't good for anything, Mr.
Elite.
Trust me, I'm gonna go crush
their group dynamics completely.
So, you're one of those women.
Have you already forgotten
you were almost kidnapped?
Best case, you'd be married.
Worst case, they own you.
You say some really scary things.
How about you just leave this to
me and go ahead to your place?
Uh...
I don't know, it doesn't feel right.
No matter how strong you are, it's not
cool letting you go face danger alone.
Tachibana...
There's just...
there's this part of you that's so...
How can I put it?
So thoughtful and kind.
It's fine, you can leave this to me.
I can find a way on my own.
I'll make it work
Do things for others be willing to
sacrifice yourself to make that happen.
That's just how I was raised
I've never even questioned it and yet man.
They're making you handle
all the paperwork again
Tachi Banna, they're supposed to
be two of you doing this, right?
So where's the other guy?
He's a team practice.
He ran out on you, huh?
And now they're just using
you come on hand him over
Huh I'm in the going
home club and when I get
there I got nothing to
do I'll help even you!
Think these are a pain
right I'm so sorry to put
all this on your shoulders
you're just so mature!
Jinguchi I end up relying
on you sorry I got team
practice I feel bad but
the tournament's coming up?
Well in that case I'm compiling stats
from the future plans questionnaires.
That's best if you don't ask
me to do stuff like statistics.
Could you staple them for me? Nice.
That I can do.
Even though he knew it would be a pain,
he couldn't pretend not to notice.
He's a person who will do things
for others when it really counts.
Instead of being someone who just
does as they're told, like me.
Honestly, he's always like this.
So cute.
I'm in love.
Let's get married.
Wait, what was that
reaction just now? Cute?
I mean, I guess that's
acceptable, but marriage?
Are you an idiot?
It's too soon to get married.
We haven't even dated yet
Why?
It's getting worse by the minute.
My thoughts are filled with Tachibana.
Is this the curse, too?
Hey!
You good, buddy?
Tachibana!
Right now, if I catch
even a glimpse, I might...
Man, looks like it hurts.
Cuts on the forehead really
bleed a ton, don't they?
Tachibana, you're just so...
I think...
I...
I can't!
It's an enemy raid!
I...
You...
You should cherish yourself more!
What are you talking about?
Why is your chest so recklessly exposed?
What if you catch a chill?
Well, I mean, it's not like I want
to dress like this, you weirdo!
Ah, falling out between comrades?
There's only two of them, and
one of them is actually a woman.
Looks like we didn't need to
call everyone out here after all?
But hey, gents, the woman's
quite a looker, isn't she?
Seems she takes care of herself.
We lucked out.
Take the woman alive!
Kill the man!
No!
No little! Take that!
Don't touch my comrades! Take that!
Kinda looks like he's planting
rice paddies. Garnish!
Huh? Be brave!
I have convinced the people of
the village to come to your aid!
It's the chief!
Take that!
Stay away from Tachibana!
Take a day!
You're acting like a
total weirdo right now!
Are you okay?
Am I? Yes.
It's true, something isn't right.
It's burned into my
eyes, I can't unsee it.
What's burned into your eyes?
It's your... Wait, me?
My what?
Well, it's kinda...
I can't really say.
This is totally my fault.
Just admit it, Jinguji.
If you're being honest, you think I'm
super cute and charming, don't you?
Nope.
I don't think you're cute at all.
Unconvincing.
Jinguji, look up.
Look up?
Wait, what's this? Charmed?
Charmed.
Listen, I know this will sound like an
excuse, but I want you to understand.
I have no interest in young girls.
It's completely outside my preferences.
And blondes really aren't my thing.
But your hair is so soft and
beautiful, and the way it shines,
even at night it illuminates your face.
It's like, since the
change, you are my son.
This is terrifying.
People can't even control their
own thoughts and feelings?
Is this how the charmed effect works?
Seriously, the power of my
looks is way too strong.
This is crazy!
I have to do something before anything
really bad happens. Tachibana.
Sorry, Jinguuji.
I mean, I was in a panic, but I think
I may have slapped you too hard.
No, I have to take some
responsibility for that.
More importantly.
You're better?
I guess so.
You don't have to be so hard on yourself.
I've never experienced a
disgrace of this magnitude!
What a blunder?
Drink up, here!
We really need to come up
with some countermeasures.
I'd rather not get slapped again.
Getting better after being hit!
Man, you're like a broken television.
Shut up!
All right, already.
There's no use crying over spilled milk.
I say we switch gears. Right now.
Let's get drunk on the taste of victory!
Would you just look at this?
It's amazing!
Do you think it might be
the currency of this world?
I don't know, but they've
hoarded quite a lot.
So, what do you think we
should do with this booty?
I think you should have it.
We'd like you to accept
it as our tribute to you.
Please say you will.
Hold on a minute.
I don't need all this stuff.
To be honest, I can't say we
didn't hope for compensation,
but it's pretty clear that all of this
must have been pillaged from this area.
Don't you see?
You're the saviors of our village.
Won't you allow us to repay you? Huh.
When you put it that
way, it's hard to refuse.
Oh, in that case, I've just
thought of something I want.
What'd you think?
It's totally modest and
it fits me like a glove.
Oh, some new clothes.
I suppose it's all right.
Jinguji, you're doing this
to save face, aren't you?
That's part of being vulnerable
to my charms, isn't it?
This guy.
He plays it so cool, but inside he
finds me so cute he can't even stand it.
This is awesome!
It feels so good!
I had no idea being this cute could
make a person feel omnipotent!
Okay, that hurts!
You win!
I give up!
What was that supposed to be?
Well, I'm sure it's a bummer knowing
someone's figured out your weakness.
Guess it's a good thing that it's
only me, then, wouldn't you say?
Hey, Hunt, do you smell something weird?
Fire!
Jinguuji, this is bad!
Fire! There's a fire!
Hey, Jinguuji!
Well then, someone's
figured out my weakness.
That's the first time
this has happened to me.
Stop that!
This is not the time to be
basking in your emotions!
Is it morning?
Satayna, are you there?
I'm right here.
As beautiful as ever, lucky me.
Premier um?
Yes, yes.
You're as lovely as ever, right?
I'm tired of hearing that.
Oh no, that isn't well.
Then let's get out there and work.
Premier, we shall work for the sake
of this beautiful elven forest.
It's a TOTALLY BURN TO THE GROUND!
Let's go!
Yeah! Fabulous! Fabulous!
Oh, my God. I'm sure. I'm sure.
Oh, yeah.
Who are you? Who are you?
Prince, you are so cute. My God.
To her, finally stop.
Love like that love, not love.
To who and that love, have not to
be too easy. My God. Who are you?
To you, to you?
How are you?
Bep do you to?
To you.
Wow, you're deep.
A little bit different,
I'm sure you're here?
It's a big deal!
You can't do it, but you can't live.
You're so happy, you and you?
What's wrong?
I saw one in my room!
One of those things that starts with C!
Calm down, open the door, spray
some peppermint oil See, it ran!
The real question is, in this world,
no insects Should we have
released that thing into it?
Destroying an ecosystem is not okay!